One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
We were able to escape from the set course
along the boundary between sky and sea.
Now we're rowing our way
to a hidden adventure at the dark bottom of the sea.
Doesn't it sound fun just thinking about it?
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
That feeling we had when we set sail
is something I'll never forget.
Because of that
nothing will be able to scare me...
Now, as the trip approaches, our racing heartbeats
engrave a rhythm of adventure in our shy hearts.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Fill your empty heart with dreams.
Spread your wings.
If you color your heart with the blowing wind
you will move on.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Perona's Terror!
Usopp vs. the Ghost Princess!
You...
How come you can fly?
Such confidence...
You were running away from me a while ago...
Why the sudden change?!
I was a bit distracted a while ago.
I never thought someone immune to the negative ghosts could exist.
I have only one thing to tell you...
Cheer up!
Shut up!
So what if you can fly?!
I'm a sniper!
Whether you fly or dance, I don't care!
Allow me to explain!
My new weapon Kabuto gains both range and stability thanks to these five axes!
When the Breath Dials I got from Sky Island are activated at the moment of firing,
rotation is added to the bullet, making all kinds of speed changes possible, creating a Super Pachinko!
Flame, flash, impact.
By changing the dials, I can make the bullets stronger!
No one can escape its abilities!
Now, prepare yo-
She's gone!
Where'd she go?!
Behind you.
Hurry and try to hit me.
W-What the hell are you?!
You damn...
Deadly...
Swallowtail Meteor!
She went back to normal!
You...
I'm gonna shoot you down!
Mantis Meteor!
Her hands are sinking into my body!
H-How come?!
I don't even feel pain!
I'm...
Already... done for!
You fool, look closer.
There's no external wound.
My hands are just inside your body.
It means your death is at hand.
Right now, with my own hands, I'm going to...
crush your heart.
Stop!
Please stop it!
That'd kill me for real!
I'm going to kill you.
Now...
Die in agonizing pain!
No!
Please stop!
I don't want to...!
Of course I can't do such a thing.
A bluff?!
I hit my head!
If I had the ability to do physical harm like crushing...
You would have died the instant my hands went into your body.
Either way, this is bad for the heart.
I just went through...
Your body.
Even though you can see me clearly...
My body can go through anything.
Deadly...
Six Chain Viper Star!
Didn't I just tell you I can go through anything?
Stop!
It's creepy!
In other words, your attacks can't hit me.
You bastard!
Go away!
Damn!
Stay away!
Go away, damn it!
What're you gonna do now?
Your attacks have no effect.
Shut up!
You bluffed about crushing my heart a while ago!
In that case, you can't touch me either!
You can't attack me either!
You can't attack!
Right?!
Mini Hollow...
W-What is that?
Ghost Rap...
T-The... wall...!
A-A blast...?!
Go away!
Rap...
You bastard...
Deadly...
Fire Bird Star!
Damn!
This is so unfair!
I'm unable to attack her!
But she can attack me back!
What kind of matchup is this?!
M-Move!
I can't see what's in front of me.
Move!
Ghost Rap...
What's this...?
It's shameful...
I thought that woman was weaker than me!
Bear!
Be careful,
Kumashi's strength exceeds that of a common bear.
What's this...?!
No one in the crew could stand up against that woman's ability...!
She was supposed to be someone only I could defeat...!
You can't...
You can't expect to beat her with your inferior abilities.
This was supposed to be my chance... but look at me...!
No use...
It's no use!
I have no chance to win!
If I'm defeated here, she'll go capture Luffy and the others, then the crew will be finished...
Saving them was a heavier burden than I thought...!
Save me...
Save me...!
Sogeking!
Please show me!
What would you do?!
Oh, the wind carries my name
from Sniper Island far away.
Kumashi!
Stop!
When I take aim, it is straight and true,
You! How dare you hurt my Kumashi..!
lu lu la la lu.
What's with that stupid mask?!
Whether you're a man or a mouse:
Lock on!
I will put your heart in my sights,
There's nothing stupid about it!
Lock on!!
Pleased to meet you!
My name is Sogeking!
Don't take me for a fool!
The man who came from the Sniper Island...
You expect me to believe you're someone else?!
Time to run!
And now you run?!
Lu lu lu lu lu la la!
Calm down!
Fight, Usopp-kun!
Shut up!
It's no use!
I can't win at all!
That's not true!
You're the only man who can do it!
Do you even have a basis to support that?!
No.
So you don't!
Mini Hollow!
Just think for a second.
There's definitely something suspicious about that woman.
That's for sure...
That woman became so confident all of a sudden.
At first she was afraid of me and ran away.
If she was immune to my attacks, then she wouldn't need to run.
She could have flown or gone through walls.
But she was crying while running away instead.
Rap!
The moment I lost track of that woman...
Something happened...
Back when I was dealing with the bear...
That's when I lost sight of her... for a moment.
Well then, it's about time I take you to Moriah-sama.
That's it!
I've solved it...!
Are there any suspicious places nearby...?
Like a secret room...
Your trick!
What's that? Your last words?
Wait!
Where are you aiming?!
That's it!
Hey, wait!
Deadly Atlas Meteor!
I've found it!
That's your real body!
If you're capable of flying,
going through walls and people...
changing from big to small as you please...
that means your body is that of a ghost!
But when I think of how you ran from me earlier...
Stay away!
At that time you were in your physical body!
What do yo-
Which means!
The person before me...
Is merely a ghost you created while I took my eyes off you.
You've kept your body concealed in there!
You can't hide the truth anymore!
I thought you were just a negative idiot...
Did you draw courage from that stupid mask?
I'm surprised you could figure it out.
But you're only 90% right...
I'm not a ghost that can be controlled by my body...
I become separated from it through Astral Travel.
A hollow that can think and act for itself.
I see!
Then, without a body to return to,
I wonder what will happen to you...
I'm sure you'd tell me not to attack it, right?
Bastard! Stop!
Deadly...
Great Explosion Star!
That was close...
You missed, though it was a dud.
One more shot!
Like I'd let you!
Special Hollow!
Is this a...?!
Mini Hollow...
Extra-large version of those things?!
This is bad!
Let go of me, bastard!
Struggle for a while.
I won't let you touch my real body.
Wait a sec!
Those dumpling-sized ghosts already caused insane damage!
If this insanely huge thing explodes, my body'll be blown to pieces!
Struggle all you want, you can't touch it...
It's a ghost.
Let go!
Let go of me, damn it!
It's a shame, Nega-nose.
When I snap my fingers, your body will be blown to pieces.
Kamikaze Rap!
It disappeared?!
That was close.
Your attack is now within this dial!
What do you-
I can't move!
What is this?!
The Great Explosion Star I shot you with was a lie!
It wasn't a dud...
It was my Sticky Substance.
That way you wouldn't be able to move even if you returned to your real body.
What did you say?!
Now I can take out both your body and hollow!
Damn!
So you're the rat who purified Commander Kumashi?!
Just in time!
Get him, Vice-commander Noble-hippo!
Impact!
Is this guy... truly that strong?!
It hurts!
I'm gonna lose my arm!
Noble-hippo!
Deadly...
Black Luster Star!
Cockroaches!
Also called Cockroach Star.
Disgusting!
Someone get them off!
Help me!
I can't get away!
It crawled inside my clothes!
I hate cockroaches!
I'm scared, so scared!
Kumashi!
Don't get scared over simple cockroaches...
Your real nightmare is...
Me!
You underestimated me too much.
I'm a man best known in East Blue for my Super Strength!
T-Ten ton...?!
H-Hey, where did you get all that strength?
S-Stop!
There's no way I'd survive that!
That'd kill me, hey!
Take the cockroaches away!
Also take that hammer away!
Take the cockroaches and the hammer away, please!
Us
o
pp...
Stop!
I won't lay a hand on your friends ever again!
Really! Really!
Please! Please! Usopp-sama!
Golden...
Pound!
So, the Princess of a Haunted Mansion...
can't help but faint over a balloon and some toy cockroaches.
You were wrong...
If you thought you could beat me in a duel of negativity and lies!
Sweet dreams until daybreak!
Didn't that samurai just say something?
In other words...
what does this mean?
It means...
the match is over!
I've never seen a battle like this!
That samurai...!
never took me seriously!
5 minutes ago,
at Hogback's lab
Shuusui: Autumn Water
So you're going to take my famous blade Shuusui?
To be more precise...
I'll be taking the blade lying beside your corpse.
I see.
You seem pretty confident about it.
D-Don't provoke him...
You carry three swords it seems.
Yeah, but one is broken.
It doesn't feel right to just throw it away, so I keep it with me.
I'm a Three Swords Style user.
Three Swords Style?
Never heard of it.
Some kind of acrobatics perhaps?
It's a shame I can't show it to you.
That nose of yours would be broken already.
Probably... you seem rather strong.
An unfamiliar sensation is boiling through my body.
As if I were about to confront a huge beast...
What a strange feeling.
I'm very excited.
That surprised me!
Aubade...
Dawn Serenade
Coup Droit!
Straight Thrust
A-A pistol?!
A-A thrust!
Nothing like that ever happened when I used that technique!